rateyourescort.org 2010-01-17

# Rate Your Escort | Privacy And Policy

#### Terms and FAQ

A. My picture/ad is online and I was not aware of it? **  
** We can't determinte the true identity of posters. If there is any personal information/picture that is publicly available without your consent, we reserve the right to remove this information as soon as we can. If this is ever the case, volunteer administrators will do the best to satisfy such requests at shortest time possible. 

**B. Someone has left a bad review. Can I have it off?**   
All reviews/comments that are found offensive or inappropriate will be removed.  
The following, but not limited to, will be considered as offensive: inappropriate language, negative feedback with no detailed information, obscene language, irrelevant comments, comments revealing identity excluding business number and business email, discriminatory comments.   
Due to limited resources we are not able to screen all comments. It is ad owner's responsibility to report any inappropriate comments which will be followed by removal by our volunteer administrators as soon as possible. However, for fairness and valid reviews we do not remove _reviews_ if we have a genuine reviewer and the review is not offensive or does not apply. The review board belongs to community and is managed by volunteer administrators. Administrators are not required to satisfy all requests. Users signing up accept the risk that bad review/comments are posted to their profile. 

**C. What information do you collect, how is it collected and how do you use it?**   
Anyone can visit our site free of charge. You are welcome to browse others' reviews and read comments without ever giving us your individual information. But we do need to gather some information about users who wish to leave comments and reviews. We collect information directly and through cookies but this is only to enhance your experience in the web site. Your information will not be shared anyone.

First, if you want to rate something, we will ask you to provide your email. We collect this information for security purposes only. We reserve the right to remove your reviews and comments without notice. If proof is available to us, reviews from anyone under 19 will be removed from the system.

One of the reasons we ask for your e-mail address is so that we can communicate with you and possibly send you the latest information about _Rate Your Escorts_. If you don't want to hear from us, we promise to leave you alone! Many of our members, however, enjoy getting news from us and being informed of special promotions or opportunities.

Second, when you register with _Rate Your Escorts_ , a "cookie" may be placed on your computer. Cookies are bits of information that a web site places on your computer's hard drive for record-keeping and activity-tracking purposes. Cookies cannot be used to learn your identity unless you have previously provided that information to that web site or your web browser automatically provides that information. Other web sites, including some of our advertisers, may also place cookies on your hard drive, but if you have not previously provided your identity to the web site and your browser does not automatically provide your identity, an advertiser will not be able to use a cookie to learn your identity.

We may also collect log files that identify information such as IP address, browser type, domain name, referral URL, country of origin, pages visited, entry points, and exit points, but we do NOT link those files to personally identifying information.

We plan that, from time to time, we will provide certain companies (like our advertisers) with aggregated user information, but this will NOT contain any individual information. We will NOT give advertisers or anyone else personal information about you without your specific authorization to do so, except as specifically described in this Privacy Policy. While we don't do it now, we expect that one day other businesses may ask us to do things like "broker" on-line focus groups, in which we may invite some users to participate (if they have chosen to be notified of those opportunities).

Our site may occasionally request information from users via surveys or sweepstakes. Participation in these surveys or sweepstakes is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving your use and satisfaction of this site.

Of course, notwithstanding anything in this policy to the contrary, we will provide personal information if we are or believe that we are legally required to do so pursuant to a subpoena, warrant, other legal method or applicable law. 

**D. How is my privacy protected when I leave comments?**  
_Rate Your Escort_ will allow you, the user, to leave comments explaining your opinions. By entering your email when leaving comments you accept the responsibility of sharing it with the owner of the listing. Rate Your Escort is not responsible for any action that happens beyond this point. Please remember that when you post comments they are publicly available, so you should exercise caution when deciding to write anything personal about yourself. This includes your email address in the body of your reviews. By placing an email in the body of you take responsibility for such action. Emails that are not in body of the review message are not publicly available. However, They can be used by ad owners as a contact email.   
**  
E. How will I know if you change your privacy policy?**  
This privacy policy may be revised over time as new features are added to the Web site. We will post those changes prominently so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post the notice we will also email users, who have aggreed to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. 

F. What kind of security measures do you take? **  
**Any information you provide, other than information you chose to provide and make publicly available in your posts, is maintained and accessible only by us, and only by those of our employees with a need to have access to such information in the performance of their work. This site has instituted commercially reasonable security measures to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control or in our possession. Although we take measures, such as those described in this Privacy Policy, to protect your personal information, we can not warrant the security of information that you provide. Accordingly, you agree that you are providing such information at your own risk. 

G. What are the limits of your Privacy Policy?   
The _Rate Your Escort_ Web site contains hyperlinks and advertisements that, if activated in the manner provided by your browser, will cause your browser to access and display the contents of other Web sites. _Rate Your Escort_ does not control or have any knowledge concerning the provisions of the privacy policies, if any, of those sites. Accordingly, _Rate Your Escort_ is not responsible for the privacy practices or any of the content of those Web sites and _Rate Your Escort's_ Privacy Policy does not apply to those other sites. If you choose to activate a hyperlink to another Web site, you do so at your own risk and you may wish to review that site’s privacy policy.   
  
H. How do I opt-out of your communication lists? **  
**As mentioned previously, _Rate Your Escort_ provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners during the registration process. Users can also remove themselves from our e-mailing list by writting to us. 

**I. What if I have more questions?   
**If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us. 

J. How can I be sure that you adhere to your Privacy Policy? **  
**If for any reason you believe that _Rate Your Escort_ has not adhered to the principles contained in this Privacy Policy, please notify us. We will do our best to address your concerns and to confirm and correct the problem promptly. 

K. How can I disable my profile  
When you sign up, you agree that you will be responsible for your own profile. By logging in to our site, you can disable your ad, update personal information, and therefore you won't require our help. We will gladly help, but we currently don't have the resources to manage this site every working day. If there are any problems, you may contact us. We will answer all the emails in the order that they are received, and as soon as we can.
